But over here, we also have a generator image option. So let's try this one out as well. I come
Over here and ask it for
Let's say
copilot
Dear copilot I
Need an image of a let's say
donkey
cooking
launch
in
a
Chicken let's say and I want the photo to be as funny as possible, right?
So let's measure the chat box humor as well as
funny as possible and I
Click generate image as well
Bro, where's my command
You just removed my command. It's so stupid. Whatever. So I
create I click generate image and this time I say create an image of a donkey
cooking launch
I want it to be as funny as
possible the humor thing, right and I send my command and I
Wait to see how it responds
So as you see whipping up a hilarious donkey chef scene and we need to wait a little bit
Until we get exactly what we want, right?
So this is the image that copilot
Generated us a donkey cooking, right? So let's say that
Again, I click generate image and I say create an image of the exact same thing but a
Way more real image the reality
And the seriousness are what I'm looking for the humor in
so regenerate place and
If you had if you pay attention, I did not give it the command again
So I want to say I want to see if it goes back to the context and understand
What I want it probably does, right? So we again, wait a little bit
Rendering a hilariously serious donkey chef in full realism
Okay, this is better. This is actually better. Yeah, it's actually a little bit funny
but
Whatever yeah, but this is pretty much all that we got with these AI tools and
This is what we got with copilot as you see it's again very smooth
Wow
Look at the image. It's all it's also downloadable from here as you see and it's very smooth